http://www.agentk-12.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy for TopSchoolJobs.org
TopSchoolJobs.org is owned and operated by Editorial Projects in Education Inc. (EPE), publisher of Education Week, Teacher Magazine, and edweek.org.
Our address is:
6935 Arlington Road, Suite 100
Bethesda, MD 20814
We can be reached via e-mail at: jobshelp@topschooljobs.org
This Privacy Policy applies to TopSchoolJobs.org and its job-search, resume and application functions; the edweek.org Privacy Policy governs other portions of the edweek.org site.
Personally Identifiable Information
TopSchoolJobs.org collects personally identifiable information from users on a voluntary basis only. This information allows us to provide users with private and secure areas to post and modify their jobs and resume. When posting a resume, our users decide for themselves how much information they wish to display.
In certain areas of TopSchoolJobs.org, such as those in which you complete a profile, submit your resume or create a new account, we will request that you provide us with certain personal information. This information may be used by EPE for marketing of our own products to you, but it is never shared with other organizations for commercial or any other purpose unless you choose to voluntarily display or distribute it.
Users should be aware that when they voluntarily display or distribute personal information (such as their email address or resume, that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which EPE is not responsible.
Job seekers may elect to make their resume searchable by TopSchoolJobs.org customers on a confidential basis only. In this case, the user's name and contact information will not be displayed to customers performing searches on TopSchoolJobs.org. (Certain other resume information such as education and experience will be displayed.) If the customer desires to contact the confidential job seeker regarding an employment opportunity, they will send an e-mail to the job seeker through the TopSchoolJobs.org system. TopSchoolJobs.org will forward the e-mail to the seeker's e-mail address. The seeker's e-mail address will not be provided directly to the customer.
Non-personal Information
In order to perform various TopSchoolJobs.org functions effectively, we may set "cookies." Cookies are small sets of data that are placed on your computer in order to keep track of what you view while on our site. Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information about you, and we do not use them for any purpose other than your convenience in posting a job or accessing content (i.e., job posting or resume that you'd like to edit.
Our web server does automatically collect information about which pages are visited and the domain name (e.g., aol.com) of visitors. We use this general information only for traffic statistics and similar internal purposes. We may track usage in aggregate based on demographic data provided by users.
Disclosures
EPE has a relationship with Madgex., a third-party Internet application service provider. As a result of your visit to TopSchoolJobs.org, Madgex will collect only such personally identifying information about you as you supply. This information may be used by EPE to communicate with you (i.e., about an order placed by you on TopSchoolJobs.org or for marketing our products to you), but Madgex may not use the information to communicate with you for commercial or any other purposes.
EPE has a relationship with The Ad Wizard, a division of InPrint Media Sales Ltd. The Ad Wizard is a third-party Internet application service provider. As a result of your visit to TopSchoolJobs.org, The Ad Wizard will collect only such personally identifying information about you as you supply. This information may be used by EPE to communicate with you (i.e., about an order placed by you on TopSchoolJobs.org or for marketing our products to you), but The Ad Wizard may not use the information to communicate with you for commercial or any other purposes.
EPE also has a relationship with DoubleClick, Inc., a third-party ad-serving company. As a result of your visit to our site, DoubleClick may collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type, and whether you responded to the ad delivered. DoubleClick does not, however, collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. For further information, visit DoubleClick's Web site at http://www.doubleclick.com.
Product order forms you fill out on TopSchoolJobs.org will normally be protected under an industry-standard secure process. (Your browser is part of this process, which is usually indicated by a picture of a closed lock, key, or similar symbol.) Your personal information and credit card information is encrypted when you send them to us through a secure page.
If our information practices ever change, we will post the changes to our Web site and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should periodically check our Web site, or write to recruithelp@TopSchoolJobs.org
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, contact us by sending an e-mail to recruithelp@TopSchoolJobs.org. top
-->
-->
-->
-->
